Everything to lose. Everything to prove.
The Redeem Team is a documentary film directed by Jon Weinbach.
Using unprecedented Olympic footage and behind-the-scenes material, The Redeem Team tells the story of the US Olympic Men's Basketball Team’s
quest for gold at the 2008 Olympic Games in Beijing following the previous team’s shocking performance four years earlier in Athens.
Self - USA 2008, played by Kobe Bryant.
Self - USA 2004, played by LeBron James.
Self - USA 2004, played by Carmelo Anthony.
Self - USA 2004, played by Dwyane Wade.
Self - Head Coach ‒ Duke University (1980-2022), played by Mike Krzyzewski.
Self - USA 2008, played by Chris Bosh.
The Redeem Team is a 2022 American documentary film directed by Jon Weinbach that chronicles the
2008 United States men's basketball team's journey during the Beijing Summer Olympics.
The film focuses on the team's effort to reclaim its dominance in international
basketball after a disappointing bronze medal finish at the 2004 Athens Olympics.
The film explores themes of based on true story, basketball,
sports documentary, basketball team, olympic sport.